Guide to the Urban and Regional Planning Department records, 1961-1993 RG0101
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Urban and Regional Planning Department records
1961-1993
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Dept. of Urban and Regional Planning
RG0101
21 Linear Feet
Collection includes original construction drawings for Gelman library and 2000 Pennsylvania Avenue, student forms, handbook for preparing theses, syllabi, newsletters, departmental history, articles, community project files (Washington, D.C. and neighborhoods), and slides.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from Urban and Regional Planning Department.
Historical Note
The Urban and Regional Planning Department was created in 1968. It was discontinued as a department in the early 1990s.
Scope and Contents
Materials in this collection includes original construction drawings for Gelman library and 2000 Pennsylvania Avenue, student forms, handbook for preparing theses, syllabi, newsletters, departmental history, articles, community project files (Washington, D.C. and neighborhoods), and slides. This collection covers the years 1961-1993. Much of this material was transferred to University Archives by Professor Stephen S. Fuller. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into four series: two series of Departmental files and one series each of Drawings and Slides.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Color slides; Washington (D.C.); Melvin Gelman Library; Campuses; Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); George Washington University; 2000 Pennsylvania Avenue (Washington, D.C.)
- Drawings, 1971-1980; RG0101 Series 1; 0.5 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains construction drawings. This material dates from 1971-80. These original construction drawings are for Gelman Library and 2000 Pennsylvania Avenue. This material is from the School of Business and Public Management, Urban Planning and Real Estate Development.
  - Gelman Library Plans, Civil, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Plans C-1 to C-5.1, six total
  - Gelman Library Plans, Architectural, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Plans A-1 to A-31, thirty-four total
  - Gelman Library Plans, Structural, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Plans S-1 to S-13, fourteen total
  - Gelman Library Plans, Mechanical, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Plans M-1 to M-20, twenty-one total
  - Gelman Library Plans, Plumbing, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Plans P-1 to P-4, four total
  - Gelman Library Plans, Utilities, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Plans U-1, one total
  - Gelman Library Plans, Electrical, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Plans E-1 to E-20, twenty-three total
  - Partition Types and Glazing Schedule, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 1.1)
    Plan 4A.1-1
  - Partition Types, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 1.2)
    Plan 4A.1-2
  - Door Types and Details, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 1.3)
    Plan 4A.1-3
  - Door Schedule, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 1.4)
    Plan 4A.1-4
  - Door Schedule, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 1.5)
    Plan 4A.1-5
  - Block Key Plan - Grade Level, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 1.6)
    Plan 4A.1-6
  - Door Schedule, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 1.7)
    Plan 4A.1-7
  - Third Parking Level West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.1)
    Plan 4A.2-1
  - Third Parking Level East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.2)
    Plan 4A.2-2
  - Second Parking Level West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.3)
    Plan 4A.2-3
  - Second Parking Level East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.4)
    Plan 4A.2-4
  - First Parking Level West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.5)
    Plan 4A.2-5
  - First Parking Level East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.6)
    Plan 4A.2-6
  - Galleria Level West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.7)
    Plan 4A.2-7
  - Galleria Level East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.8)
    Plan 4A.2-8
  - Mezzanine Level West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.9)
    Plan 4A.2-9
  - Mezzanine Level East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.1)
    Plan 4A.2-10
  - Second Floor West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.11)
    Plan 4A.2-11
  - Second Floor East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.12)
    Plan 4A.2-12
  - Third Floor West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.13)
    Plan 4A.2-13
  - Third Floor East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.14)
    Plan 4A.2-14
  - Fourth, Fifth, & Sixth Floor West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.15)
    Plan 4A.2-15
  - Fourth, Fifth, & Sixth Floor East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.16)
    Plan 4A.2-16
  - Seventh Floor West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.17)
    Plan 4A.2-17
  - Seventh Floor East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.18)
    Plan 4A.2-18
  - Eighth Floor West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.19)
    Plan 4A.2-19
  - Eighth Floor East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.2)
    Plan 4A.2-20
  - Nineth Floor West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.21)
    Plan 4A.2-21
  - Nineth Floor East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.22)
    Plan 4A.2-22
  - Roof & Penthouse West Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.23)
    Plan 4A.2-23
  - Roof & Penthouse East Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.24)
    Plan 4A.2-24
  - First Parking Level - Paving Pattern, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.25)
    Plan 4A.2-25
  - Galleria Level West - Paving Pattern, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.26)
    Plan 4A.2-26
  - Galleria Level East - Paving Pattern, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.27)
    Plan 4A.2-27
  - Second Floor West - Paving Pattern, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.28)
    Plan 4A.2-28
  - Second Floor East - Paving Pattern, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 2.29)
    Plan 4A.2-29
  - Core Plans West, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 3.1)
    Plan 4A.3-1
  - Core Plans West, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 3.2)
    Plan 4A.3-2
  - Core Plans East, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 3.3)
    Plan 4A.3-3
  - Core Plans East, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 3.4)
    Plan 4A.3-4
  - Stair Plans, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 3.5)
    Plan 4A.3-5
  - Galleria Level West Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 4.1)
    Plan 4A.4-1
  - Galleria Level East Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 4.2)
    Plan 4A.4-2
  - Mezzanine Level West Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 4.3)
    Plan 4A.4-3
  - Mezzanine Level East Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 4.4)
    Plan 4A.4-4
  - Second Floor West Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 4.5)
    Plan 4A.4-5
  - Second Floor East Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 4.6)
    Plan 4A.4-6
  - First Parking, West & East Cores Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 4.7)
    Plan 4A.4-7
  - Galleria Core Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 4.8)
    Plan 4A.4-8
  - Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 4.9)
    Plan 4A.4-9
  - High Rise South, West and East Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.1)
    Plan 4A.5-1
  - High Rise North Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.2)
    Plan 4A.5-2
  - Low Rise North Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.3)
    Plan 4A.5-3
  - Low Rise North Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.4)
    Plan 4A.5-4
  - Low Rise North Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.5)
    Plan 4A.5-5
  - Low Rise North Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.6)
    Plan 4A.5-6
  - Low Rise West Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.7)
    Plan 4A.5-7
  - Low Rise South Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.8)
    Plan 4A.5-8
  - Low Rise South Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.9)
    Plan 4A.5-9
  - Low Rise South Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.1)
    Plan 4A.5-10
  - Low Rise South Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.11)
    Plan 4A.5-11
  - Low Rise East Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.12)
    Plan 4A.5-12
  - Existing Building Alteration, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.13)
    Plan 4A.5-13
  - Existing Building Alteration, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 5.14)
    Plan 4A.5-14
  - Toilet Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 6.1)
    Plan 4A.6-1
  - Interior Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 6.2)
    Plan 4A.6-2
  - Building Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.1)
    Plan 4A.7-1
  - Stair Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.2)
    Plan 4A.7-2
  - Stair Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.3)
    Plan 4A.7-3, missing
  - Elevator Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.4)
    Plan 4A.7-4
  - Detail Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.5)
    Plan 4A.7-5
  - Galleria Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.6)
    Plan 4A.7-6
  - Galleria Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.7)
    Plan 4A.7-7
  - Galleria Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.8)
    Plan 4A.7-8
  - Galleria Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.9)
    Plan 4A.7-9
  - Stair Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.1)
    Plan 4A.7-10
  - Low Rise Wall Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.11)
    Plan 4A.7-11
  - Low Rise Wall Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 7.12)
    Plan 4A.7-12
  - Exterior Detail Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.1)
    Plan 4A.8-1
  - Exterior Detail Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.2)
    Plan 4A.8-2
  - Exterior Detail Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.3)
    Plan 4A.8-3
  - Exterior Detail Sections, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.4)
    Plan 4A.8-4
  - Window and Column Details, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.5)
    Plan 4A.8-5
  - Exterior Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.6)
    Plan 4A.8-6
  - Skylight Elevations, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.7)
    Plan 4A.8-7
  - Skylight Details, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.8)
    Plan 4A.8-8
  - Skylight Details, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.9)
    Plan 4A.8-9
  - Low Rise Bldg. Exterior Details, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.1)
    Plan 4A.8-10
  - Low Rise Bldg. Exterior Details, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.11)
    Plan 4A.8-11
  - 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 8.12)
    Plan 4A.8-12
  - Elevator Cab Details, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 9.1)
    Plan 4A.9-1
  - Elevator Cab Details, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 9.2)
    Plan 4A.9-2
  - Expansion Joint Details, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 10.1)
    Plan 4A.10-1
  - Miscellaneous Details, 1981 -1982 (Box 2, Folder 10.2)
    Plan 4A.10-2
- Departmental files, 1968-1993; RG0101 Series 2; 19.5 Linear feet
  This series contains student forms, handbook for preparing theses, syllabi, newsletters, departmental history, articles, community project files (Washington, D.C. area neighborhoods, etc.). The material dates from 1968-93. This material comes from the Urban Planning and Real Estate Development Government program.
- Slides, RG0101 Series 3; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains slides. The dates cover 1968-81. These more than 400 slides are images The George Washington University buildings, the University Yard, campus and the Foggy Bottom neighborhood, images of George Washington, models and plans of campus area land use. This material comes from the School of Business and Public Management, Urban and Regional Planning.
  - Buildings: I Street and Pennsylvania Ave., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Buildings: Academic Center, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Buildings: Alumni House from Yard, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Buildings: Athletic department, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Buildings: Building "C" (Funger Hall), 1969 -1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Buildings: Building "J" on G Street, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Buildings: Buildings on G and 21st, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Buildings: Columbian University 1884, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Buildings: Corcoran Hall - East facade, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Buildings: Edison Building, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Buildings: F Street Club, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Buildings: Funger Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Buildings: Future Fine Arts quad, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Buildings: Gelman Library, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Buildings: Grant School, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Buildings: GWU Campus Club, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Buildings: GWU Clinic - Penn. Ave. and 22nd street, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Buildings: GWU Hospital, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Buildings: GWU Hospital entrance on Penn. Ave., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Buildings: GWU Medical Center, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Buildings: H Street building from Yard, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Buildings: Hall of Government, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Buildings: Henry Building-21st and Eye Street, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Buildings: International Student Services building-G Street, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Buildings: John May House-18th and F Street, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Buildings: Law Library - 20th Street, 1968 -1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Buildings: Law Library - west facade, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Buildings: Lenthall Houses, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Buildings: Library, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Buildings: Lisner Auditorium, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Buildings: Lisner Hall facing north, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Buildings: Lisner Hall-old Library, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Buildings: Lisner Hall-portal west side, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Buildings: Lisner Library, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Buildings: Marvin Center, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Buildings: Marvin Center looking east, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Buildings: Marvin Center roof, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Buildings: Marvin Center Sculpture, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Buildings: Monroe Hall (front and back), 1977 -1979 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Buildings: Monroe Hall (sketch), undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Buildings: New Greek House, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Buildings: Old President's Office, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Buildings: PEPCO building, 1972 -1976 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Buildings: Red Lion Row, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Buildings: Rice Hall, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Buildings: Ross Hall, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Buildings: Samson Hall - east side, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Buildings: School of Government and Business Administration, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Buildings: Smith Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Buildings: Student Center (Marvin Center), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Buildings: Tin Tabernacle, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Buildings: Tompkins Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Buildings: Townhouse - 21st and G, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Buildings: United Methodist Church/old Communications department, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Buildings: View west to 21st street, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Buildings: Women's Gym - 23rd street, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Buildings: Woodhull House, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Buildings: Woodhull House, Campus Crossroads, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Buildings: Woodhull House-rear, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Campus Scenes: 19th and F streets-GWU sign, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Campus Scenes: 19th and H Street, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Campus Scenes: 19th between F and G streets, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Campus Scenes: 19th between F and G streets-Town house west side, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Campus Scenes: 20th and F streets, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Campus Scenes: 20th and G streets, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Campus Scenes: 20th and G streets view west, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Campus Scenes: 20th between G and H streets, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Campus Scenes: 21st street, 1972 -1975 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Campus Scenes: 21st and Eye, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Campus Scenes: 21st and F streets, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Campus Scenes: 21st and G streets-kiosk, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Campus Scenes: 21st and G streets view east, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Campus Scenes: 21st and H streets, 1972 -1975 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Campus Scenes: 21st at Marvin Center, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Campus Scenes: 22nd and G street - view east, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Campus Scenes: 22nd and H streets-Northeast corner, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Campus Scenes: 22nd street between F and G streets, undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Campus Scenes: Alley between G and H streets, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Campus Scenes: F Street between 21st and 22nd, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Campus Scenes: F to G Street, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Campus Scenes: G Street (2000 block), undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Campus Scenes: G Street (2000 block)-Police C. box, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Campus Scenes: G Street (2018), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Campus Scenes: G Street between 20th and 21st streets, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Campus Scenes: G Street front Lisner Library, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Campus Scenes: G Street-south side between 20th and 21st streets, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Campus Scenes: GWU Directory board, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Campus Scenes: H Street, 20th and 21st street, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Campus Scenes: I Street-northside, undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Campus Scenes: K Street at 22nd, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Campus Scenes: Lafayette Square, undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Campus Scenes: Library, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Campus Scenes: Library Ct., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Campus Scenes: Library-from behind, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Campus Scenes: Marvin Center ramp, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Campus Scenes: Marvin Center roof garden, undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Campus Scenes: Metro-21st Street and Pennsylvania Ave., undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Campus Scenes: Various scenes, undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Campus Scenes: Monroe Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Campus Scenes: Monroe Quad, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Campus Scenes: Monroe Yard, 1970 -1972 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Campus Scenes: Monroe Yard-21st entrance, 1972 ca. (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Campus Scenes: Monroe Yard-Courtyard behind Monroe and Government, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Campus Scenes: Parking lot and garage, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Campus Scenes: Parking-between 19th and F streets, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Campus Scenes: Parking-new garage, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Campus Scenes: Parking-South of Building "C", 1972 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Campus Scenes: Pennsylvania Ave. and 21st Street, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Campus Scenes: Quad-21st Street entrance, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Campus Scenes: Quad-Aerial, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Campus Scenes: Quad-Lisner, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Campus Scenes: Quad-View from Lisner Hall, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Campus Scenes: Quad-View from Stuart Hall, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Campus Scenes: Quad-View North, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Campus Scenes: Row houses on F Street, undated (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Campus Scenes: Row houses on G and 20th street, undated (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Campus Scenes: South wall of Corcoran Hall, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Campus Scenes: University Yard, 1969 -1972 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Campus Scenes: University Yard from "H", 1972 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Campus Scenes: University Yard from 21st, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: F Street-18th and F-Northeast corner, undated (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: F Street-21st and F-NW corner, undated (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: F Street-22nd and F-Old TKE house, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: F Street-between 21st and 22nd, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: G Street-1920 Concordia Church, undated (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: G Street-20th and 21st, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: G Street-20th and G., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: G Street-Street Furniture, 22nd and G street, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Allen Lee Hotel, 23rd and F street, undated (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Decatur House, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Edson building, undated (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: IMF building, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: 19th and Pennsylvania Ave., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: 20th St. between F and G, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: 21st and Eye, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Alley on 20th between F and G looking east, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Church entrance on 20th between H and Pa. Ave., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Columbia Plaza, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Eye St. and 20th, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Fire Station rear, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Proposed World Bank building, 32882018319262 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Retail surplus supply store, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Typical buildings, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Various scenes, 1977 -1981 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Watergate building, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Octagon House, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Washington Circle, undated (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Washington Circle-22nd street, undated (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Washington Circle-23rd Street, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Foggy Bottom Scenes: Washington Circle-Pennsylvania Ave., undated (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Images of George Washington: 35 Silver Washington by Roy Frank Finger, 1975 -1976 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Images of George Washington: Cloud Cover by Roy Frank Finger, 1974 -1976 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Images of George Washington: Crisis in Common Sense by Zuka, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Images of George Washington: Eleventh George, 1975, Icon of the Father of Our Country, by Stefstahl, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Images of George Washington: George #1 1973, George #5 1973 by Stefstahl, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Images of George Washington: George #7 and George #10 by Stefstahl, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Images of George Washington: George in Drag by William Dunlap, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Images of George Washington: George in the Blue Room by James Sundquist, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Images of George Washington: George Washington by Edward Savage, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Images of George Washington: George Washington by JBT (Unident Artist), ca. 1855, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Images of George Washington: George Washington by Michael Clark, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Images of George Washington: George Washington by Rembrant Peale, ca. 1820, undated (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Images of George Washington: George Washington Monro-Lenox Portrait by Gilbert Stuart, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Images of George Washington: George Washington-glazed ceramic by Robert Arneson, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Images of George Washington: George Washington-marble sculpture by Herbert Barbee, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Images of George Washington: George Washington-sculpture by Ulysses Darbanze 1965, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Images of George Washington: George Washington-silk tapestry by Philippe Albert Fonson 1848, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Images of George Washington: George's Ark by Joan Danziger, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Images of George Washington: Green George Washington by Michael Clark, 1973 -1976 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Images of George Washington: GW at Trenton-needlepoint by John Atrumbull, ca. 1840, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Images of George Washington: GW Grouping by Michael Clark, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Images of George Washington: GW Tree by Rosette Bakish, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Images of George Washington: Impossible Star by Roy Frank Finger, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Images of George Washington: Washington's Crazy Quilt by Sante Graziani, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - GW People: Elmer Louis Kayser, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - GW People: William W. Corcoran, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 176)